[Disclaimer:
All depicted events are fictional
and for entertainment purposes only;
viewer discretion is advised]
[Your Third Series]
I'm turning 23 this year.
It's not my unlucky year yet,
but it seems like my life
is constantly being tested.
I can speak five languages,
going global like a diplomat's son.
I've done all sorts of extreme activities,
and now, I'm working as an assistant secretary
for Mr. Sib, Sattawat Adisuan,
an executive at
a top-tier consumer goods manufacturer.
Drowning?
I will surface.
Burning?
I won't get burnt.
Getting hit by a truck?
I can dodge it.
Lost in the woods?
I have my own GPS.
It's built into my watch.
I'm prepared for any situation.
You speak five languages?
Indeed.
Thai?
Hello.
My name is Jam. It's nice to meet you.
Chinese?
Hello. My name is Jam.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
English?
Hello, my name is Jam.
Nice to meet you.
Spanish?
Hello. My name is Jam.
Pleased to meet you.
Japanese?
Hello. My name is Jam.
I'm eager to learn from you.
On top of that, I am a really fast learner.
[Adisuan Group]
Welcome to 'Adisuan Group.'
Thank you.
[Mr. Sib]
Mr. Sib.
Yes, Mr. Sib?
My husband has been hospitalized
due to a seafood allergy.
Please take over for me.
No problem.
Mr. PiMai.
Hello, Mr. Jam.
Hello, Mr. PiMai.
Was the trip here rough?
It wasn't at all.
From what I saw on soap operas...
Have you eaten yet?
I thought a boss's spouse
must be fussy and get agitated easily.
I have.
However, Mr. PiMai is such a sweetheart
and is surprisingly soft and kind.
Mr. Sib?!
Where is PiMai staying in Chiang Mai?
I need an answer in five minutes.
Understood!
PiMai has a wrist injury.
Keep him company for a bit, can you?
Take this as a change of pace.
Yes, Mr. Sib.
Am I his assistant secretary
or his superhero on demand?
Mr. Jam?
Can you wrap your own wrist?
Is your wrist still hurting?
Uh...
Well... It still kind of is.
I hope you get well soon.
[Adisuan Group]
Take a seat, Mr. Jam.
Thank you.
Lately, Adisuan Group
has been losing its footing.
"I may disappear for a while.
No need to look for me.
This wounded tiger
needs time to nurse his wounds.
I will return when I am fine."
Take a look at this.
Yes?
That...
It's from my younger brother.
Mr. Sarm?
What happened to him?
Well...
He probably wanted to take his time off, as stated.
Adisuan Farm
has been having problems lately
since its owner has vanished
into thin air for months.
No one knows where he is.
He has abandoned his job.
He probably has forgotten...
what his responsibilities are.
It'd be fine if he was gone for just a while.
But it's been way too long.
Adisuan Group can't simply wait like this.
Should tiny problems go unresolved,
they will cause a domino effect
that ruins everything.
In two weeks,
Namnueng, my sister, is getting married.
She takes the word "family" very seriously.
This means that
all of the siblings must show up.
Mr. Sarm...
must be brought back.
Having worked together,
I'm sure you have strong persuasive skills.
You can easily convince people
and win them over.
This quality of yours is second to none.
Don't say that word, please...
I...
Please, no.
I want you to bring Mr. Sarm back to us.
But you are brothers.
You might have an easier time
convincing him than I do.
You have a group chat.
Please talk to each other, boss...
If I have to do everything with my two hands,
then what's the point of having you around?
Okay.
It's just a special mission.
Let's look on the bright side.
Just thinking about it...
already gives me chills.
Sib, you're not going to kiss your husband?
Kiss him.
Kiss him. Kiss him.
Kiss now. Kiss now.
Kiss now. Kiss now...
Kiss him...
Kiss him.
Kiss him. Kiss him.
Kiss him now. Kiss him now.
Kiss now. Kiss now.
Very lovely.
By the way...
Who are you?
My name is Jam,
and I'm Mr. Sib's assistant secretary.
And...
do you know who I am?
If I have to guess...
you must be one of Mr. Sib's twin brothers,
and you are working as a doctor
at Pakchong Hospital, correct?
You are sharp
and quick-witted.
Are you two going to talk all day?
And...
Do you know...
who this guy
actually is?
That is Mr. Sarm,
your younger twin brother, Mr. Song.
He is now in charge of
all of Adisuan Group's operations,
including the gigantic orange orchard
and the food processing factories...
Enough already.
It's annoying.
Good at organizing, huh?
Was it you...
who set them up to be together?
Sarm...
What do you mean I set them up?
Mr. Sib and Mr. PiMai love each other.
And what is it that makes you upset?
Let go!
If you don't want to get hurt,
don't act like you know everything.
Easy now.
Please don't hold it against him.
That's who he is.
Right.
What are you doing here,
Snoop?
I am sorry,
but my name is Jam, not "Snoop."
I am here to pay Mr. PiMai a visit,
as any caring friend would.
When did you two get close?
It's because you're like this.
What else would I call you but "Snoop"?
Wait...
Oh!
How about "Snoopy Jerk"?
Mr. Sarm...
Did Sib send you to spy on things?
I think the reason I'm here...
is of no concern to you.
Quite a sharp tongue.
Know this, you.
As long as you are at Adisuan Farm,
I can release my beaked friends
to peck you whenever I please.
Well, know this, Mr. Sarm.
If I'm harmed in the slightest,
all that will be left here is nothing but ashes.
Oh, you.
Hey, Mr. Sarm!
What did I tell you?
"If you don't want to get hurt,
don't act like you know everything."
I'll tell you one more thing, then.
If you don't want to live a hard life,
then don't act so tough with me.
Beep-beep.
Beep-beep, beep-beep, beep-beep.
Would you like to go bird watching with me?
I would love to.
Don't go too far, alright?
Yes.
Come on.
Let's go.
This way, please.
Birds by the garden...
Don't be dishonest with your feelings.
If you want to follow
your husband, then go.
Let them have fun on their own.
Hey, Sib...
Do you really love PiMai?
If you don't, let him go.
I won't, and I will never.
Just say it already, damn it.
Say it out loud!
Just let me hear it already.
If you don't love him,
let him be mine.
That's for saying without thinking.
And that's for having
nasty thoughts toward my man.
- Mr. Sib!
- Dear Sib...
Did something happen?
It was nothing.
A busted lip isn't gonna kill him.
Into the house.
But Sarm...
It is okay, Mr. Sarm.
It is but a minor injury...
like being stung by ants.
You think we're friends?
Hey!
Drive for me.
You aren't going to do it yourself?
I can't.
My heart's too weak.
That's ridiculous.
What's really wrong with you?
Well, I'm officially heartbroken.
Gosh...
I'm okay.
I'm fine.
Thank you.
Wait for me, please!
All I have to do is bring Mr. Sarm back
for the Outstanding Employee Trophy.
How hard can it be?
Kiss him. Kiss him. Kiss him.
Sarm!
Don't do the unthinkable, Sarm!
Please don't die, Sarm!
Sarm!
Sarm!!
Sarm...
Damn it.
Sarm!
Sarm, you're gone?!
It's too soon, please!
What are you doing here?
Sarm.
You were gone!
I came to bring you your lunchbox,
but you weren't home.
So I followed you here.
I'm worried about you.
Let go, Lantao.
I refuse!
I told you to let go.
- No!
- Hm?
I said, "Let go."
Never!
"Hands off," I said!
No!
Let go.
I won't!
Let go of me.
Never!
- Hands off!
- I said no!
I didn't mean it.
Sarm, wait for me, please!
Sarm!
Wait for me, please!
Sarm.
Lantao.
I brought you food.
Go home already.
Your dad's worried about you.
I refuse.
Just go ahead and take a shower.
Do you have any idea that
you are bothering me?!
And I'm slightly annoyed.
Sarm, you're one big meanie!
Can't I just be in peace?
I got interrupted
while relaxing in the sea.
I didn't even get to drink my pain away.
This sucks!
[Ms. Namnueng's wedding is only 14 days away]
It's been four days,
and I haven't made any progress.
Am I ChatGPT to him or what?
Today, I'm here in Pak Chong District
because I'm meeting a handsome man
who has captured
everyone's heart.
This person
is the owner of the gigantic Adisuan Farm,
which is known for its accommodation,
restaurants,
attractions, and activities.
It covers the full spectrum of both agriculture
and tourism businesses.
And this person
is right here. It's Mr. Sarm,
Traiphop Adisuan!
Remember my name
because my golden era is here.
And my slogan is...
"Mighty
and glorious.
It's Traiphop."
Alright...
That introduction
was totally grand and unforgettable.
Yes.
You're still as friendly as you've always been.
Of course.
If that is the case, I would like you
to give us a tour of Adisuan Farm
if you don't mind.
With pleasure, really.
I'll show you
every nook and cranny of this place.
But first,
"An army marches on its stomach."
I am going to take you
to try exquisite dishes
at our country-style garden restaurant.
Our restaurant
offers dishes...
of the finest quality.
The meat we serve is from our very own farm.
The quality of the meat goes without saying.
Because it's premium quality?
It's good old local meat.
- Huh...
- Mm.
If I have to guess, the meat
must be very tender, correct?
Well, you can already tell without having a bite.
Whoa, is it because it melts in the mouth?
- It melts before you get to eat it.
- Huh...
Okay.
Mr. Sarm, you are quite comedic yourself.
Just keeping it casual.
I have heard that
you also sell fresh meat directly from the farm?
Indeed.
If our viewers at home
would like to recreate your dishes,
do you keep your recipes a secret?
Do I? Well, I don't.
But we really can't give you our recipes.
Why is that, you may ask?
Because...
"our dishes are tasty
'cause we forgot the recipes."
- Alright.
- Right.
Today, you're going to give us
a tour of Adisuan Farm,
stretching across three districts
in Nakhon Ratchasima.
The orange orchard takes up
70 percent of the entire land.
It's as far as the eye can see,
surrounded by overlapping mountain ranges.
You can see
how far he has taken the farm.
- Right.
- Working this hard,
do you even have time to rest at all?
I'm a human, alright?
Of course, I need some rest.
Mm.
Between the mountains and the beach,
where would you rather spend your time off?
I prefer the beach.
It is, without a doubt, the beach
because...
when I was little,
I would often spend time with my mother
in her hometown in Chon Buri
during school breaks.
Whenever...
I need time to think
or deal with what's on my mind,
I go to the beach.
And the beach at night, in particular,
is my absolute favorite.
It's peaceful.
Do you go there with your sweetheart?
Oh.
"I'm single...
but not completely."
Oh...
This means that...
you do have someone in your heart, correct?
You can say that, yes.
Alright, everyone.
Alright, that was a nice little introduction
to Mr. Sarm, Traiphop Adisuan.
- Before we go, Mr. Sarm,
- Yes?
could you leave a piece of advice
for the passionate young people
watching us right now?
No problem.
"You catch more flies
with a net than with honey."
"I'm single...
but not completely."
This means that...
you do have someone in your heart, correct?
You can say that, yes.
It is but a minor injury...
like being stung by ants.
You think we're friends?
That's ridiculous.
What's really wrong with you?
Well, I'm officially heartbroken.
Where is he crying his eyes out right now, I wonder?
[I may disappear for a while.
No need to look for me.
This wounded tiger needs time
to nurse his wounds. I will return when I am fine.]
This wounded tiger
needs time to nurse his wounds?
To know more about this wounded tiger...
I need to enter its cave, don't I?
My mission to bring
the teeny-tiny tiger back home
has begun!
No matter where you are hiding,
I'm coming to bring you home.
Dad.
Mom.
I'm leaving for work.
Please wish me smooth sailing.
Where on earth is
the Human Resources headquarters?
Oh.
Jam.
Hello, Dr. Song.
Hello.
You can simply call me by my name.
Would it be okay?
Of course, it would.
Well...
I don't see you as Sib's assistant,
but as PiMai's friend.
Just address me
the same way he does,
okay?
Right.
Excellent.
Now, then...
What are you doing here?
I've actually been wanting to meet you, Dr. Song.
Mr. Sib tasked me with bringing Mr. Sarm home.
That is why I want to talk to someone close to him.
Did you read his note?
Mm, yeah.
I didn't expect him to fall for PiMai this much.
By the way,
how exactly are you going to look for him?
I'm not sure.
But I started by
hiring a private investigator.
And the report just came in.
It appears that Mr. Sarm hasn't left the country.
Do you have ways to contact him, Dr. Song?
Someone like Sarm
cuts off all communication, Jam.
He's actually isolating himself for real.
Mm, though...
I do understand him.
It's his first heartbreak,
so it hurts a fair bit.
Mm...
Dr. Song,
is it possible for me
to meet Mr. Sarm's assistant?
Sarm
doesn't have an assistant.
He hates being nagged.
He manages everything himself.
But if you want to get
an overview of Adisuan Farm,
I'll take you to Thee.
Mr. Thee?
He's the general manager of this farm.
Has he been working here for long?
Well...
It was when Sarm came back from his studies
that Thee started working here.
He is Sib's cousin, around the same age.
Speaking of Thee,
a few days ago,
he almost got into a fight with Sib.
Fortunately...
Sib had an urgent trip to Chiang Mai.
So nothing happened.
Why were they fighting?
At that time,
Sib sent someone to audit the accounts,
and Thee was very upset,
seeing that as an interference with his work.
Actually, it is hard to say
because several years ago,
this place almost didn't make it.
They needed Sib
to be their lifeline for years.
It was when Sarm returned
that the business flourished once more.
Sarm, oh, Sarm.
Just because he disappeared,
everything got chaotic.
Based on my twin sense,
I'm guessing that
he's probably taking some time off,
getting stung by jellyfish on some beach.
On some beach?
That's my two cents.
It has to be a beach in Thailand, too,
as right now,
Father is sick.
So it's unlikely for him to leave the country.
A beach in Thailand...
Or is he residing at a vacation house in Chon Buri?
Definitely not.
Sarm is an extremist.
When he does something,
he always goes all out.
And when he wants to run away,
he'll run away as far as he can go.
This means that
Chon Buri and Hua Hin are out of the equation.
So that leaves the beaches in the South, then.
Would you believe
that I can tell what task Sib will give you
once you manage
to bring Sarm back?
What task will it be?
He probably has you stay at the farm.
It's to...
bring faith back to the workers
and restore the tarnished image of Sarm.
Don't stress out, Jam.
Right.
We lost track of time while chatting.
Please come have some food with me.
I just came back from the hospital,
and I'm starving.
I could eat a horse right now.
Fortunately, that stupid horse
is nursing his broken heart.
Otherwise, he would've been done for.
I'll join you.
Let's go.
Right.
Hello, Father.
Oh, hello.
This is Jam,
Sib's assistant.
I remember you now.
You're so talented for your age.
You can definitely work with Sib.
Truth be told, Mr. Decha,
it's working with Mr. Sib
that brought out the best in me.
Mm, well said, really.
Straight to the point.
This young man is starting
to take a liking to you, you know?
Oh.
I mean, "this uncle."
This young uncle, I mean.
- Right...
- I'm starting to take a liking to you.
We seem to get along well.
- Mm...
- Right, Father.
Jam is actually Sib's right-hand man.
Recently, he ordered Jam
to bring Sarm back home.
I think...
Sarm
will definitely return
before Namnueng's wedding.
That would be lovely, wouldn't it?
Excuse me.
The feng shui master is here.
Please, have a seat.
Who is this individual?
Uh...
How is he related to the family?
He is the assistant
of my older brother.
Mm...
You have good features.
The signs are clear.
I've never seen such clear signs before.
Soon,
this person
is destined to hold power
within the Adisuan family.
Remember my words.
However, before obtaining such power,
it is best to tread lightly.
It's not your unlucky year yet,
but danger awaits.
You are fated to suffer
the same misfortune as your parents:
either by falling into the water
or by drowning.
Recently,
you have been given
an impossible task, correct?
He's being a bit dramatic, isn't he?
Feng Shui Master, you spoke
as if you actually knew
what kind of accident
my parents were involved in.
That's only natural.
Before becoming a feng shui master,
I was a medium
and a shaman.
Seeing things beyond
the ordinary was my specialty.
Would you like me to read your future?
My reading is accurate.
What you said is true.
I've been dealing with a task
that is extremely challenging.
And I'm wondering if I'll succeed.
Of course, you will.
With great success as well.
But it'll come
at the cost of your soul.
What does that mean?
That's all I can say. Bye.
I'm out. See ya.
Please wait.
What is it?
I guess...
I need to take a shot
and see what I can find out about Mr. Sarm.
An island in the South...
Can you pick one for me?
Ko Pha-ngan.
I know all. I see all!
The stars have spoken!
Ko Pha-ngan is the destination!
Confused?
Do not be, for I shall explain it to you.
The Full Moon Party.
Affordable tickets
with convenient transport.
Oh, yeah?!
Handsome men are there.
Have you been there?
Yes, quite often, actually.
You can simply set off there now!
Thank you, Ghibli,
for staying with me all night.
See you soon.
Bye-bye, boo.
[Uncle Mai's Kitchen]
Peekaboo!
You're here to make up with me?
Sarm.
Never do that again.
I was simply clinging to your arms.
Well, I don't like it.
Fine.
And...
What would you like to have?
Go get me some alcohol.
You drink, too?
What a bad boy you are.
You ran out of drinking yogurt or what?
Now, you know...
what your life is like without me,
don't you?
By the way...
Now that you ordered a drink,
would you like to munch on me
as a snack as well?
Gosh... Lantao.
How many times must I tell you not to do this?
Focus on your studies, please.
Why do you always forget
that I've already graduated?
I want to work with you.
What do I have to do?
Reconsider.
Why?
"To work with me, you'd have to be tough.
Getting hit by a truck should be easy stuff."
Think you're up for this,
huh?
All is fine by me.
I really want to be your assistant.
How about this?
How about you try working with Sattawat?
If you last a month,
I will consider it.
I'd rather not.
What a shame.
Go get me a drink already.
Give me that.
Don't drink too much, Sarm.
I need to go help my dad first.
Then, I'll be here as your boyfriend...
Oh!
As your friend, I mean.
See you.
- Hey!
- Your beard...
It tickles!
Excuse me.
May I sit with you?
I want to be alone.
Please...
Let's see...
Tell me
you're not interested in this sexy body.
Enough of this.
You want me to touch it?
Hey!
You harassed my boyfriend?
He touched my butt.
Got anything to say?
You know who I am?
You don't even know
who the hell you are.
And you expect me to know...
who you actually are?
What's your name?
My name is...
Three.
Damn it...
Hey!
Where are you?!
This way.
Groping someone else's lover?
You think you're hot shit?
Is your father that big a shot?
Well, my father isn't.
But...
I am.
Big!
Jeez!
Fucking big, you said.
Big enough for you, alright?
When I do something, I always go all out.
I go all out when it comes to love.
I go all out when I'm in pain.
And tonight, I'm going all out on this guy.
How about you get some of this?
Someone's losing their head tonight!
Ghibli...
Ghibli.
Thank you, Ghibli.
Ghibli. Oh...
You become a person?
You're human...
An owl transformed into a human.
What are you on about?
Let go.
You're Ghibli.
- Hey...
- Ghibli, Ghibli.
Come here.
- Ghibli. Oh!
- Come here.
There are two of you?
- Ghibli. Ghibli.
- Ghibli, my ass!
Whoa!
Ow.
Ah...
Thank you for punching me, damn it.
I'm sober now.
But next time, don't.
- Ow...
- Right!
Seeing you getting hurt
already satisfies me.
What's done is done.
Damn it... Come on!
Let's go, babe.
Get up! You're so heavy!
You're flattening me!
Snoop.
What have I done to deserve this?
Someone actually found me?
I'm here to take you home.
And you must come with me.
I'm not going with you.
Go back where you came from.
We can do this the easy way,
or we can do this the hard way.
Jiranat!
What is it,
Traiphop...?
Don't get too cocky, Snoop.
Ow...
That's how you speak to a senior, huh?
Go build a sand castle, boy.
You never stop treating me like a little boy.
I'm already 23 years old.
I have a job
and duties.
And I've been handling them very well,
- Oh...
- unlike you.
You abandoned your work
and duties.
Shouldn't you be ashamed of yourself?
Seriously.
What's in your mouth?
Razor blades?
Let me take a look!
Let me see it!
Open your mouth and let me see.
- Huh?
- Let's see why you are this foul-mouthed.
- Let me see it.
Here I come.
What a foul mouth you have.
So do you.
- Stinky!
- Right. Oh...
The manager informed me that
a drunk person had caused a scene.
I thought it was some thug,
but it was you, Sarm.
Are you hurt?
I'm good.
Who dares hurt you, Sarm?
From now on, I'll be the one protecting you.
Save yourself first.
Your dad's here.
What is it, Uncle?
Words travel fast, don't they?
He's worried about his son-in-law, alright?
Oh...
Don't get ahead of yourself, son.
You turned my place
into a boxing ring or what?
Care to watch a match or two?
Still joking?
By the way, are you hurt in any way?
My heart's been through worse.
Allow me to treat your injuries.
I'll serve you right at your place.
And that should impress you.
And what about you?
Are you alright? Are you hurt?
Oh, you probably can't speak Thai, can you?
Lantao, ask him
what his mix is.
He's half human, half ghost.
And what about you?
What half-animal are you?
Why did you say that to Sarm?!
Watch your tongue.
Don't push your luck, Snoop.
Do you think we're friends?
Last I checked, I don't work for you.
And even if I did...
you have no right to say
such vile things to me.
You threw rocks at me,
so I threw the rocks back,
not some beautiful flowers.
Perhaps...
I should call you...
"Sarmonkey?"
Sarmonkey?
You called him a monkey?
Why did you call him that?
The last guy who said that didn't end well.
And the ones
who said bad things to me
are now recovering in the ICU.
Wait...
Still talking this much
even after I ripped your mouth?
Next time we meet,
I'll make sure you can't talk.
You're all bark and no bite.
Let me tell you something.
You got away this time
because I let you go.
If I had chosen not to,
you wouldn't have slipped away.
Do you think prey
can escape the claws of this mighty tiger?
Roar!
Who's that, Mister?
My older brother's assistant.
He's here to bring me home.
You're going home already, Sarm?
As long as my heart isn't healed,
I'm not going anywhere.
It seems like
a lot of people
have been looking for you lately.
Don't tell me that guy...
And you said it was over.
Don't let me find you.
Where the hell are you?
Huh?
You want your fate to end at a hospital?
- It's not him.
- What?
Then who?
It's whatever, then.
I don't really care anyway.
I'm leaving to see Ghibli.
I miss Ghibli.
Wait, Sarm!
What is it?
You looked really cool.
You're certainly the king of all tigers.
You have a good eye.
I'll be going now.
[Mission: Hunt Down the Teeny-tiny Tiger]
My mission has officially begun.
Now, I know that Mr. Sarm didn't disappear
just to leave everything behind.
Instead, he's running away from his heart.
What I just learned is that
he has cut himself off from everyone.
He hasn't returned home or to the farm.
He doesn't want anyone
to look for him either.
But at the same time,
his family is waiting for him,
and so is the work he left behind.
Many people are waiting for his return.
The only clue I had was the beach,
as he'd always go there
to heal his broken heart.
I have no idea if this trip will end with me
being able to bring Mr. Sarm home
or becoming the one
who mends the heart of this "wounded tiger."
I have found Mr. Sarm. He is on Ko Pha-ngan.
It's time to end this mission
by bringing the teeny-tiny tiger home.
I'm not returning.
Please, Mr. Sarm.
If you do, my mission will be complete.
If you are not coming home today,
then when are you going to?
Hey, hey.
It's damn near impossible...
to track you down,
Mr. Sarm.
♫I'm here to love you as myself,
not as a surrogate♫
♫Let me be your safe space
when you need a break♫
♫Who cares if I'm not your first or second?♫
♫At least being your third still counts♫
♫I'm here to love you,
no matter who left you with heartache♫
♫Just let me heal your heart,
lending you my aid♫
♫Have faith and believe in love once more♫
♫'Cause good love is your Lucky Third♫
♫Your Third, can it be me, love?♫
[Your Third Series]